You survived in the underworld by being quick to switch sides.
And now you've chosen this crew as your next haven.
Every organization that she's had something to do with in the past has been annihilated.
Pistol!
You have some very loyal friends, but you will never change, will you, Nico Robin?
No! That's not true!
Robin!
I'm not who I am!
Duel between rubber and ice. Luffy versus Aokiji.
You bastard!
Stop yelling. If you thaw her out carefully, she'll live.
However, her body is extremely fragile in this state, so you'll need to handle her with care.
If any part of her breaks, she'll die.
For example, if I were to smash her apart like this...
Robin!
No!
Stop!
Uh?
That was close!
Oh, my!
That was amazing, Usopp!
What in the hell are you doing?
Usopp!
Chumper!
Quick!
Take Robin and run back to the ship!
Throw her out and keep her safe!
Right!
You got it, Captain!
Hurry!
Be gentle, okay?
It's cold!
I know, but Robin's even colder, genius!
Don't bother. The world would be a much better place without that woman in...
Not to split hairs, but a pirate crew pretty much consists of people just like that.
You got that right, lady. Now, if you don't mind, kindly step aside.
Nami! You're not gonna mess with this crew!
Wait! Nobody attack him!
Huh?
Stay back and don't interfere. I'm gonna fight him one-on-one.
What do you want?
What do you want to do, isn't it?
Oh, oh, I'm gonna fight him!
No!
I'm gonna fight him!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Look!
It's just a pirate crew.
You got that right, lady.
Now, if you don't mind, kindly step aside.
Ah!
Nami!
You're not gonna mess with this crew!
Wait! Nobody attack him!
Huh?
Stay back and don't interfere!
I'm gonna fight him one-on-one!
What do you want to do?
What do you say?
The two of us can settle this on our own.
Fine by me.
But since I don't have a ship to take you back,
then I'll just have to kill you.
She can't breathe like this, can she?
I think she's in a state of suspended animation.
Doesn't that mean she'll die if we don't do something?
If we warm her up too quickly, she'll shatter.
We have to restore her body temperature from the inside out.
Are you sure that this is really going to work?
I don't know, but it's the only thing I...
Whoa, wait a minute. You don't know?
This is Robin's life we're talking about here.
I know, but I've never treated someone
whose entire body was frozen before.
I know that Aokiji said she was still alive,
but I just don't see how that could be possible.
Don't give me that crap.
If you can't do anything to save her,
then no one in the whole world can.
You understand me?
You are the doctor of the straw hat pirates, got it?
I know, okay? Just shut up and stop yelling at me!
Chopper!
What's going on? Why are just the three of you here?
Where's Luffy?
There's no time to explain.
We need to go back right away.
Help us do something about this frozen arm and leg.
Oh, right.
We...
We need to douse every part of your body
that's frozen in water.
But we're using the shower room for Robin.
How is Robin? Is she okay?
Uh, it's too early to tell.
What are you doing?
Will this do chopper?
Yes. Once the ice begins to melt,
start rubbing the affected areas
and then come up to the ship right away.
Nami, come aboard and help us treat Robin.
Right.
What the...
Why are you guys here?
What happened?
Where's Luffy?
Fighting out Kiji one-on-one.
One-on-one?
You mean you left Luffy there
to face him all by himself?
Those were the captain's orders.
Are you crazy?
Can't you tell when an order is unreasonable?
I can't believe you would be so cold-hearted
as to just leave a head.
It was a duel.
Can't you understand that?
It's what he wanted.
Stop it, both of you.
This isn't the time.
Right now, we need to stay focused, okay?
Whether this decision was one of his passing whims or not,
it doesn't matter.
Whatever happens,
we have to be ready to deal with it.
Understand?
You really are an odd one, aren't you?
Now it's ice time.
What do you say?
The two of us can settle this on our own.
Oh, man.
You tricked me.
The moment I agreed to fight you one-on-one,
I settled on defeating you and you alone.
But that was your plan, wasn't it?
If I were to attack your crew now,
I'd be the bad guy here.
Isn't that right, Captain?
Or maybe you actually thought you could beat me.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
Keep a close eye on Nico Robin.
Eventually, she'll grow to be more than you can handle.
The nature of the violent fate she was born into
will be a greater danger than you can imagine.
More of a burden than you could ever hope to bear.
That's what it means to have that woman as part of your crew.
You have been warned,
Mr. Monkey D.
Mr. Monkey D. Luffy.
It would be easy to break you and kill you right here and now.
But I have a debt to honor.
Consider us even for you taking care of Crocodile.
As well as...
Well, never mind.
Something to do with Smoker.
See ya.
There he is!
Luffy!
He's still in one piece!
That's good news!
I'll carry him!
Let's get him to the ship!
Stop saying what I'm saying!
If they follow their log pose from this island,
their next destination is...
It's Water 7.
The City of Water, huh?
Oh, my, my, my.
Would you look at that?
They're getting really close to our headquarters, aren't they?
I'm saying...
What do you want?
Both... of their hearts... are beating!
Yeah!
Snoopy!
Norman!
No, you can't go in yet!
I don't want them disturbed, understand?
Hey, Dr. Chopper, how about I make them some food?
Calling me doctor won't make me feel happy or anything, you stupid jerk!
But I suppose some warm drinks would be nice for when they wake up.
I'll carry them into the lounge later.
Aye, aye, sir!
Hey, Nami, should we set sail?
No, not yet.
Not while the captain's out of commission.
The lock pose has our new heading, but let's rest here for the day.
What's wrong, Usopp?
You look beat.
Are there gonna be more guys like him?
Coming after us everywhere we go?
This is crazy.
I don't know how much more of it I can take.
Get some sleep, idiot.
You're just exhausted, okay?
Okay.
Go, go, go, go, go.
In order for Luffy and Robin to get some rest and recover, the Going Mary remained anchored off the uninhabited island for four days.
After that, we set sail.
Today marks the third morning since we resumed our voyage.
The weather is clear and sunny, mostly spring, with occasional bouts of summer.
It's beautiful!
Nami, look!
I made this potato pie especially for you, mademoiselle.
I hope you enjoy it.
Mmm, delicious!
That makes me so happy!
Hey, keep it down, jerk!
Some people are trying to sleep around here!
Sorry about that, cactus head.
My most sincere apology.
What, you cigarette snorkeling dartboard?
Huh?
What did you call me?
Dartboard.
Dartboard eyebrows.
What?
Lou!
Bee!
Woo!
We've been waiting for this!
Lou!
Bee!
Ha-ha!
This is me frozen!
I can't believe this is how he behaves after almost freezing to death!
What do you think?
You nailed it!
That's exactly what you looked like!
Make sure you clean all that up, Luffy!
Kay!
Hey, Nami, is that food?
What are you eating?
Some potato pie-ee!
Potatoes, huh?
I love potatoes!
Sanji, make me some!
Just how many hours a day do you have to lie around and sleep anyway?
That's none of your business!
I'll sleep as long as I like!
Wanna fight about it?
Okay, you two, enough!
Sanji, our captain has requested some of your potato pie-ee!
You got it, Nami!
Sanji!
Potatoes!
You're still recuperating, but that hasn't slowed down your appetite in the slightest, has it?
So this is pie, huh?
Good stuff!
Why is it called that?
Because the meat is taken from the tail of the giant beast pie-ee!
I should know, I was the one who killed it!
It was over a hundred meters long!
Whoa!
A hundred meters?
That's amazing, Uzo!
And I did it all before breakfast!
Wait, you woke up early to kill it?
Chopper, have you forgotten who I am?
Uh, oh, I get it.
You're Captain-
Yes, that's right!
I'm the great and almighty Captain Uzo!
Robin!
Good to see you!
Are you feeling okay?
Do you still have a chill?
Your treatment helped me out tremendously.
Thanks, you're a wonderful doctor.
Calling me a wonderful doctor won't make me happy or anything, you stupid jerk!
He sure looks happy.
Yep, you should take it easy, Robin.
Luffy's already recovered enough to where he's running around and screaming like an imbecile.
But you can just relax and take your time.
Yeah!
That wasn't a compliment!
Hey, Robin!
Would you like me to make you something to warm you up?
Do you have an appetite?
I do.
May I have some coffee, please?
Of course!
It's my pleasure!
Hmm?
What the heck is that?
Man!
This pie and stuff is delicious!
I can't stop eating it!
Yeah!
Oh no!
I bet we could make some money selling this stuff!
Luffy, come quick!
There's a...
There's a frog doing the front crawl!
What?
See for yourself!
It's headed to your side!
Really?
I wonder if it's that same frog we heard about!
Come on, Luffy!
Are you really gonna take anything that Goofy Admiral told you said?
It's a frog!
I wonder if it's that same frog we heard about!
Come on, Luffy!
Are you really gonna take anything that Goofy Admiral told you seriously?
There's no way a frog could do the front crawl if...
Holy crap!
There's a frog doing the front crawl!
Come on!
After him!
Take in the sails!
Stand by the oars!
Bring the ship about two o'clock!
I know!
It's a frog!
Two o'clock!
Aye, aye!
Hurry!
I don't know why, but I get the feeling we really have to follow it!
Sorry to keep you waiting, mademoiselles.
Uh, what's happening?
What the?
What's going on?
It seems like the ship has changed its course.
Hey!
What's the deal here?
Why'd you change our course without asking me?
Nami, you're never gonna believe it!
We found this huge frog with scars all over its body and we're following it!
A frog?
What?
We have to catch up to it, capture it, cook it and eat it for lunch!
You wanna eat it?
You're right!
Huh, is that a lighthouse?
Now, what is a lighthouse doing way out here?
I wonder if anyone lives there?
What the?
Do you see an island?
Not really, it's just a lighthouse.
There's not enough there for the log post to point to.
What about the frog?
Tell us which way the frog went!
Not a chance!
It looks like the frog is headed to the lighthouse.
Frogs should be marinated in white wine to dissolve the mucus.
Then you coat them with flour and fry them up crisp.
Sanji, snap out of it!
If the captain says we're going after the frog, we really don't have much choice in the matter.
Robin!
Let's go!
Full speed ahead!
Hi-hi!
Why are you all going along with this?
Hee-haw!
It's flying!
Quick, don't let it get away!
Let's get up ahead of it and block its course!
Hee-haw!
I guess we ran ashore or something!
H-h-hah!
Nami!
Robin!
Say something!
Are you two okay?
Yeah.
I think I'm okay.
Ugh.
Same.
Oh!
Thank goodness.
Huh?
Uh!
What is that sound?
What the heck? What's going on?
Wait, that sounds like a...
No way! Out here?
Full reverse right now! Turn 180 degrees!
Well, I didn't go on前 to meet these days.
I know that I
with the dashing sea train and the city of water,
Water 7.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!